Why do you refuse to obey me?
왜 나에게 순종하기를 거부합니까?
Will obeying orders change anything?
명령에 순종하면 변화가 있을까요?
In my experience, it never does.
내 경험상 절대 그렇지 않습니다.
Do your experiences prove me wrong?
당신의 경험이 내가 틀렸다는 것을 증명합니까?
Arrogant bastard.
오만한 놈.
What now?
지금은 무엇입니까?
A renowned steroid dealer has been arrested.
유명한 스테로이드 딜러가 체포되었습니다.
That's none of my business.
그건 내 알 바가 아니야.
Sir, wait!
선생님, 잠깐만요!
Though it's only a rumor,
비록 소문일 뿐이지만,
people say Sawada and Kudo were on the client list.
사람들은 사와다와 쿠도라고 말해요 고객 목록에 있었습니다.
I thought you should be informed of this.
나는 당신에게 이 사실을 알려야 한다고 생각했습니다.
Sawada, you say?
사와다라고?
President? President Negishi?
대통령? 네기시 대통령?
Isami. [YAOSHIMA Holdings Co., Ltd]
이사미. [YAOSHIMA Holdings Co., Ltd]
Isami, what happened?
이사미, 무슨 일이야?
Couldn't you have held back a little?
좀 참을 수 없었나요?
Now, I'll assume he brought this on himself.
이제 나는 그가 이 일을 자초했다고 가정하겠습니다.
But you still went a bit too far.
하지만 당신은 여전히 ​​조금 지나쳤습니다.
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
정말 죄송합니다.
No, no, no. Lift your head.
아니, 아니, 아니. 머리를 들어보세요.
Isami, it's alright.
이사미, 괜찮아.
You're a capable man. You know that, right?
당신은 유능한 사람이에요. 그거 알지?
You're not like your father.
당신은 당신의 아버지와 같지 않습니다.
I still trust you.
나는 아직도 당신을 신뢰합니다.
You understand what I mean, right?
무슨 말인지 이해하시겠죠?
Yes.
예.
Do you know what's needed when trust is about to waver?
무엇이 필요한지 아시나요? 언제 신뢰가 흔들릴까?
No, well...
아니, 음...
It's speed!
속도입니다!
Work twice as hard as yesterday!
어제보다 두 배 더 열심히 일하세요!
Yes, sir!
네, 선생님!
Be quick!
빨리!
Be nimble!
민첩하게 행동하세요!
Be superb!
훌륭해!
And shut down that baseball team!
그리고 그 야구팀을 폐쇄하세요!
I will deal with it promptly!
신속하게 처리하겠습니다!
Fantastic!
환상적입니다!
In the early hours of January 25th,
1월 25일 이른 시간,
an unemployed man was arrested
실업자가 체포되었습니다
for illegally selling muscle enhancers to professional baseball players.
근육 강화제 불법 판매 프로 야구 선수들에게.
Police have confiscated a client list from the arrested man,
경찰이 고객 목록을 압수했습니다. 체포된 남자로부터,
sending shockwaves through the Japanese baseball scene.
충격파 보내기 일본 야구 현장을 통해.
I would like you to look into Sawada's performance.
꼭 보셨으면 좋겠습니다 사와다의 연기에
I need data that will prove he was taking enhancement drugs.
증명할 데이터가 필요해요 그는 강화제를 복용하고 있었습니다.
You can do that, right?
그렇게 할 수 있지, 그렇지?
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
[12 years ago]
[12년 전]
Someone amazing just joined the team.
놀라운 사람이 방금 팀에 합류했습니다.
What's with the speed of that ball?
그 공의 속도는 어떻습니까?
One more!
하나 더!
Nice ball!
좋은 공!
- Looking good, Sawada. - Thank you.
- 좋아 보이네, 사와다. - 감사합니다.
Give me another!
또 줘!
Nice.
멋진.
Yo, promising rookie!
야, 유망한 신인!
What do you want to eat?
무엇을 먹고 싶나요?
Erm...
음...
Ramen, I guess.
라면인 것 같아요.
- Ramen? - Yes.
- 라면? - 예.
- Alright. - Thanks.
- 괜찮은. - 감사해요.
You should eat meat, though. Now that'll give you energy.
그래도 고기는 먹어야지 이제 그것이 당신에게 에너지를 줄 것입니다.
That's not good enough.
충분하지 않습니다.
What you need to hit is a live ball.
쳐야 할 것은 라이브 볼이다.
- Ready? - Yeah.
- 준비가 된? - 응.
Ready.
준비가 된.
Move your location for training.
훈련을 위해 위치를 이동하세요.
We can't afford the grounds you've chosen.
우리는 당신이 선택한 근거를 감당할 수 없습니다.
If our players train in the cold, their risk of injury increases.
우리 선수들이 추운 날씨에 훈련한다면, 부상 위험이 증가합니다.
Do not make me repeat myself.
나 자신을 반복하게 만들지 마십시오.
Move your training camp elsewhere.
훈련 캠프를 다른 곳으로 옮기세요.
[Kusanagi Sports Complex, Shizuoka]
[쿠사나기 종합운동장, 시즈오카]
Good morning.
좋은 아침이에요.
Ushiyama. Are you here to grill us meat?
우시야마. 우리 고기 굽으러 오셨나요?
'Course not!
'당연하지!
Call me Ushiyama the bullpen catcher.
나를 불펜 포수 우시야마라고 불러주세요.
I'll make your mitts sound real good.
네 미트 소리를 정말 좋게 만들어 줄게.
Don't burn your mitts!
장갑을 태우지 마세요!
I'm Kawauchi, your resident trainer.
저는 여러분의 상주 트레이너인 Kawauchi입니다.
If you feel any abnormality in your body,
몸에 이상이 느껴지면
or have any questions about muscles,
아니면 근육에 관해 질문이 있으신가요?
feel free to ask this macho man here.
여기 이 마초맨에게 편하게 물어보세요.
Now we've gotta win.
이제 우리는 승리해야 합니다.
A former Dreams star from Korea will also be joining us.
한국 출신 전 드림스 스타 또한 우리와 함께 할 것입니다.
- What? - No way.
- 무엇? - 안 돼요.
Hello, everyone. It's great to be back.
여러분, 안녕하세요. 다시 돌아와서 정말 기뻐요.
I'll be helping out as a temporary coach.
제가 임시코치로 도와드리겠습니다.
Show me what you've got!
당신이 무엇을 가지고 있는지 보여주세요!
I'm back with the Dreams!
드림즈와 함께 돌아왔습니다!
Kang Du Gil! Kang Du Gil!
강두길! 강두길!
Welcome back!
돌아온 것을 환영합니다!
These athletes supported the team when the Dreams were runner-ups.
이 선수들은 팀을 지원했습니다 Dreams가 준우승이었을 때.
Now they've returned to help you all train.
이제 그들은 여러분 모두의 훈련을 돕기 위해 돌아왔습니다.
Yo!
에야디야!
Athletes.
운동 선수.
I apologize about the campsite.
캠핑장에 대해 사과드립니다.
We're sorry.
죄송합니다.
GM, we're the only ones training in the area.
GM, 우리는 이 지역에서 훈련을 받는 유일한 사람입니다.
Will we have an opponent to practice against?
연습할 상대가 있을까요?
I'll definitely find you all one.
꼭 하나하나 찾아드리겠습니다.
Please do.
그렇게 해주세요.
- Please.
- 제발.
Nice!
멋진!
Yeah, nice!
응, 좋았어!
That's a good pitch!
좋은 피치네요!
You can throw it harder! Come at me!
더 세게 던질 수 있어요! 나에게 와라!
His slider is making over 2600 RPM's!
그의 슬라이더는 2600RPM이 넘습니다!
- Seriously? - Yes.
- 진지하게? - 예.
It was really good.
정말 좋았습니다.
But for sliders,
하지만 슬라이더의 경우
try adding a bit more pressure to your middle finger.
좀 더 압력을 가해 보세요 가운데 손가락까지.
- My middle finger? - Right.
- 내 가운데 손가락이요? - 오른쪽.
Watch my pitch.
내 피치를 조심하세요.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
Ready?
준비가 된?
Aim for the middle.
중간을 목표로 하세요.
Min Jong.
민종.
Relax.
안심하다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Min Jong, wait.
민종아, 잠깐만요.
Point your elbow outward.
팔꿈치를 바깥쪽으로 향하게 하세요.
Does that hurt?
그게 아프니?
No, sir.
아니요, 선생님.
We might make the series this year.
올해는 시리즈를 만들 수도 있겠네요.
But I worry about Min Jong.
그런데 민종이 걱정된다.
He wasn't throwing strikes.
그는 스트라이크를 던지지 않았습니다.
It may be the yips.
입스일 수도 있습니다.
[Yips: an unexplained loss of ability] [Most often seen in athletes]
[입스 : 설명할 수 없는 능력 상실] [운동선수에게서 가장 흔히 볼 수 있는 현상]
Will he recover?
그는 회복될까요?
I can't say for sure right now.
지금은 확실히 말할 수 없습니다.
Are the Dreams getting stronger?
꿈은 점점 강해지고 있나요?
I see some real potential in the team.
나는 팀에서 진정한 잠재력을 봅니다.
Then I'll keep my expectations high.
그러면 기대를 높게 유지하겠습니다.
Please do.
그렇게 해주세요.
Can we talk?
우리 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까요?
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Come sit.
와서 앉으세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Please watch this video.
이 영상을 시청해주세요.
You were off your game at the rookie training session.
넌 게임을 그만뒀어 신인 훈련 세션에서.
Does the same spot hurt now?
지금도 같은 부위가 아프나요?
Your form is breaking down, perhaps out of fear of injury.
당신의 형태가 무너지고 있습니다. 아마도 부상에 대한 두려움 때문일 것입니다.
Turn it off, please.
꺼주세요.
Don't be afraid.
두려워하지 마십시오.
You need to face the issue.
당신은 문제에 직면해야합니다.
You're facing a mental wall, kid.
넌 정신적인 벽에 직면해 있어, 꼬마야.
There's nothing wrong with your body.
몸에는 아무 이상이 없습니다.
We have another video.
또 다른 영상이 있습니다.
It's from when the GM and Scouting Director first visited you.
GM이 언제부터인가 그리고 스카우트 디렉터가 처음으로 당신을 방문했습니다.
You should still be able to throw the same pitch.
당신은 여전히 ​​할 수 있어야합니다 같은 공을 던지기 위해.
I can't.
나는 할 수 없다.
Don't let the pressure of first pick get to you.
선픽의 압박을 가하지 마세요 당신에게 다가가세요.
Your career has just begun.
당신의 경력은 이제 막 시작되었습니다.
You're rushing to see results.
결과를 보기 위해 서두르고 있습니다.
It's only your first year as a pro. Don't be so hard on yourself, yeah?
이제 프로 데뷔 첫해입니다. 너무 자책하지 마세요, 그렇죠?
Min Jong, smile.
민종아, 웃어라.
What you need on the mound is peace of mind.
마운드에서 필요한 것은 마음의 평화이다.
No one's putting you in rotation yet.
아직 아무도 당신을 로테이션에 넣지 않았습니다.
Gear yourself up for September. That's when we'll need you.
9월을 준비하세요. 그때가 바로 우리에게 당신이 필요할 것입니다.
Don't worry. I'll keep this old bod going until then.
괜찮아요. 나는 그때까지 이 오래된 회사를 계속 운영할 것이다.
- Sounds great. - Hey, no slacking for you.
- 좋은 것 같아요. - 이봐요, 게으름 피우지 마세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Gwenchana-yo.
그웬찬나요.
Yeah, that's right. I'm studying.
응, 맞아. 나는 공부하고 있어요.
What does that mean?
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
It means... "don't worry about it".
그 뜻은... "걱정하지 마세요"라는 뜻이에요.
Answer honestly.
솔직하게 대답하세요.
Are there any problems with Kudo?
쿠도에 문제는 없나요?
Yes.
예.
You...
당신은...
And what's his issue?
그리고 그의 문제는 무엇입니까?
Because you sure neglected to tell me.
왜냐면 당신이 나한테 말하는 걸 무시했거든요.
He doesn't have many game-winning hits.
그는 게임에서 승리한 안타가 많지 않습니다.
That's not what I was asking about.
내가 물어본 건 그게 아닌데.
You're awfully tense.
너 정말 긴장됐구나.
Alright, look.
알았어, 봐.
Has Kudo ever used any drugs?
쿠도는 마약을 사용한 적이 있나요?
No.
아니요.
Are you sure?
확실합니까?
Please calm down.
진정하세요.
Ever since that dealer was arrested,
그 딜러가 체포된 이후로,
our owners have gotten real antsy.
우리 주인이 정말 불안해졌어요.
They suspect Kudo is on the client list.
그들은 Kudo가 고객 목록에 있다고 의심합니다.
There's no issue there.
거기에는 문제가 없습니다.
I see.
알겠어요.
Sorry I lost my temper.
미안해요 화를 냈어요.
No worries.
걱정 마세요.
I take no offense.
나는 화를 내지 않습니다.
But in exchange,
하지만 그 대가로
I request a practice match.
연습경기를 요청합니다.
I should've known.
나는 알았어야했다.
Do you know how I feel wearing this uniform?
내 기분이 어떤지 알아? 이 유니폼을 입고?
Why are you so obsessed with the Dreams?
왜 그렇게 꿈에 집착하는 걸까요?
The Vikings can win the series.
Vikings가 시리즈에서 우승할 수 있습니다.
It's not all about money and winning.
돈과 승리가 전부는 아닙니다.
Then what exactly is so important to you?
그렇다면 당신에게 그렇게 중요한 것은 정확히 무엇입니까?
I was born in that city,
나는 그 도시에서 태어났어요,
and grew up wanting to be a Dreamer.
Dreamer가 되고 싶어 자랐습니다.
I've had fans rooting for me since I was a middle schooler.
나를 응원하는 팬들이 있었어요 중학생 때부터요.
My cheer song echoed throughout the dome.
내 응원가가 돔 전체에 울려 퍼졌다.
I'd hear kids screaming my name.
아이들이 내 이름을 외치는 소리가 들렸습니다.
Everything about me...
나에 관한 모든 것...
was a Dreamer.
드리머였습니다.
You would never understand how I feel.
당신은 내가 어떻게 느끼는지 결코 이해하지 못할 것입니다.
Kudo.
쿠도.
Good afternoon, everyone.
안녕하세요, 여러분.
The name's Itsuki Miyahara, shining star of the Dreams staff.
이름은 미야하라 이츠키, 드림스 직원의 빛나는 별.
I'm here to bring you nail-biting commentary.
여러분께 뼈아픈 해설을 전해드리러 왔습니다.
I'm joined by my co-host,
공동 진행자
the famous blogger, and now member of our data analysis team.
유명 블로거, 그리고 현재 회원 우리 데이터 분석팀의
Let's hear it for Akito Sakurazaki!
사쿠라자키 아키토의 이야기를 들어보자!
Hello, I'm Sakurazaki.
안녕하세요, 사쿠라자키입니다.
Pleased to have you here, Sakurazaki.
사쿠라자키 씨를 만나서 반가워요.
Are you nervous?
긴장됐나요?
Oh, no...
아, 아니...
We'll be reporting our Dreamer's play-by-plays,
우리는보고 할 것입니다 우리 드리머의 실황
right here from the Kusanagi Stadium.
바로 여기 쿠사나기 스타디움에서요.
Alright!
괜찮은!
Let's knock their socks off!
그들의 양말을 벗겨보자!
Go Dreams!
꿈을 꾸세요!
Let them have it!
그들이 갖게 해주세요!
Kikuchi, you'll ruin your voice.
키쿠치, 너 목소리 망칠 거야.
That's the goal! Who cares about my voice?
그것이 목표입니다! 누가 내 목소리에 관심이 있나요?
I want to convey my feelings to the players.
선수들에게 내 마음을 전하고 싶다.
Let's go!
갑시다!
Yeah, let's go!
응, 가자!
We're definitely going to win!
우리는 반드시 승리할 것입니다!
Oh, GM! Have a seat.
아, GM! 앉으세요.
You sound more desperate than our players.
우리 선수들보다 당신이 더 절박한 것 같군요.
- He got you there, Kikuchi. - Yeah, he got you.
- 그가 당신을 거기까지 데려다줬어요, 키쿠치. - 응, 그 사람이 널 잡았어.
Alright, let's do this!
좋아, 해보자!
Huh?
뭐?
Wait a second.
잠깐만요.
You're not wearing matching socks.
당신은 어울리는 양말을 신지 않았습니다.
I didn't realize that could actually happen.
실제로 그런 일이 일어날 수 있다는 것을 몰랐습니다.
I was in a bit of a hurry.
나는 조금 서두르고 있었다.
That's not my point.
그건 내 요점이 아니야.
I feel for whoever has to look after you.
당신을 돌봐야하는 사람이 누구인지 느껴집니다.
I have no such individual in my life.
내 인생에는 그런 사람이 없습니다.
Batting first, the shortstop, Arihara.
타자 먼저, 유격수 아리하라
Play ball!
공놀이!
Strike!
스트라이크!
Strike two!
투 스트라이크!
Strike! Batter out!
스트라이크! 타자 아웃!
Alright!
괜찮은!
That's our Sawada.
바로 우리 사와다입니다.
What a fastball!
정말 패스트볼이에요!
Arihara's bat didn't even graze it.
아리하라의 방망이는 스치지도 않았습니다.
Striking out the Rookie of the Year is a piece of cake for him.
올해의 신인상을 노려라 그에게는 케이크 한 조각입니다.
I'd say we've got this game in the bag.
나는 우리가 가방에 이 게임을 가지고 있다고 말하고 싶습니다.
In the bag!
가방에!
Alright, let's go for a home run!
좋아, 홈런을 치러 가자!
Nice!
멋진!
Hit it hard!
세게 쳐라!
Here we go!
간다!
Alright!
괜찮은!
Three consecutive strikeouts!
3연속 삼진!
Change!
변화!
Nice pitching!
좋은 피칭!
What an absolute show from the first inning.
1회부터 정말 완벽한 쇼였습니다.
You bet.
당신은 내기했다.
Now, it's the bottom of the first, the Dreams' offense.
자, 이제 첫 번째의 바닥입니다. 드림즈의 공격.
Get ready!
준비하세요!
- Stay sharp! - Go get them!
- 정신 바짝 차려! - 가서 가져와!
It's a hit!
히트작이에요!
The ball... it's flying!
공... 날고 있어요!
- It's flying! - He blasted it.
- 날고 있어요! - 그 사람이 폭파했어요.
And it's outta here!
그리고 여기서 벗어났어요!
Yay!
이야!
Home run!
홈런!
- Yay! - Yes!
- 예!
He did it!
그가 해냈어요!
I always believed in you!
나는 항상 당신을 믿었습니다!
The Dreams have hit a leadoff homer.
드림즈가 선두 홈런을 쳤습니다.
- They lead by one run! - Yes!
- 한 점 앞서고 있어요! - 예!
How spectacular!
정말 훌륭합니다!
Kijima! Did you see that?
키지마! 그거 봤어?
Hey, Miyata!
안녕, 미야타!
I hit that to the stands!
나는 그것을 스탠드에 쳤다!
Did no one see that?
그걸 본 사람은 아무도 없나요?
Nice homer!
좋은 호머!
My chants reached him!
내 노래가 그에게 도달했습니다!
- Move! - Nara, good job!
- 이동하다! - 나라씨, 수고했어요!
- I can't see! - Hey, careful!
- 볼 수 없어요! - 조심해!
Careful, careful!
조심해, 조심해!
Woah!
와!
Watch it!
조심해!
Get back here, Kikuchi!
여기로 돌아가라, 키쿠치!
Hurry!
서두르다!
[Vikings 0 - 3 Dreams]
[바이킹 0 - 3 꿈]
Strike!
스트라이크!
Sawada overwhelms the batter!
사와다가 타자를 압도한다!
He struck out four players in a row!
그는 연속으로 4명의 선수를 삼진으로 처리했습니다!
The Vikings are getting a sneak peek of our upcoming season.
바이킹이 살짝 엿보고 있습니다. 다가오는 시즌의.
We oughta start charging!
충전을 시작해야 해요!
Kudo's up next.
다음은 Kudo입니다.
Why is he batting fifth when he has the best stats?
그는 왜 5번째 타석에 있는가? 그 사람이 최고의 통계를 가지고 있을 때요?
The team hasn't acknowledged him yet.
팀에서는 아직 그를 인정하지 않았습니다.
It must be tough for Kudo.
쿠도에게는 힘든 일이겠죠.
I had a time like that too.
나에게도 그런 시절이 있었다.
You were a traitor.
당신은 배신자였습니다.
Former, traitor. "Former"!
전, 배신자. "이전의"!
I'm a changed man now.
나는 이제 변화된 사람이다.
Good afternoon.
좋은 오후에요.
- Good afternoon. - Afternoon.
- 좋은 오후에요. - 오후.
- Mr. Ishikura. - Apologies for the late greeting.
- 이시쿠라 씨. - 인사가 늦어서 죄송합니다.
- Welcome, welcome. - I brought him along.
- 환영합니다, 환영합니다. - 내가 데려왔어.
What a thrilling game.
정말 스릴 넘치는 게임이에요.
This is only a practice match.
이것은 단지 연습 경기일 뿐입니다.
Sawada and Kudo wouldn't agree.
사와다와 쿠도는 동의하지 않았습니다.
To them, it's a game of life-or-death.
그들에게 그것은 삶과 죽음이 걸린 게임이다.
It's always been like that with those two.
그 둘은 늘 그랬어요.
You're pitching strong.
당신은 강하게 투구하고 있습니다.
Let's kick it up a notch.
한 단계 더 발전시켜 봅시다.
Batting fifth, the left fielder, Kudo.
5번타자 좌익수 쿠도
[#7 Kudo]
[#7 쿠도]
Foul!
반칙!
Kudo is being overpowered.
Kudo가 압도당하고 있습니다.
No, Kudo is purposefully scoring fouls
아니요, Kudo는 의도적으로 파울을 범하고 있습니다
because he hasn't seen an opportune pitch.
왜냐하면 그는 적절한 투구를 보지 못했기 때문입니다.
I knew that.
나는 그것을 알고 있었다.
Strike!
스트라이크!
Yes! Strike three!
예! 쓰리 스트라이크!
Alright!
괜찮은!
Kudo must be lamenting.
쿠도는 한탄하고 있을 것이다.
"Why was I born in the same era as the monster Sawada?"
"나는 왜 같은 시대에 태어났을까? 괴물 사와다로?"
Damn it! Damn it all!
젠장! 젠장!
Okay, alright.
알았어, 알았어.
Why doesn't he take him head-on?
왜 그는 그를 정면으로 받아들이지 않습니까?
[Vikings 0 - 3 Dreams]
[바이킹 0 - 3 꿈]
Top of the third inning.
3회말 탑.
One out, runner on first.
원 아웃, 주자가 먼저입니다.
Sawada pitches!
사와다 투구!
They've grown.
그들은 성장했습니다.
Miya.
미야.
I'm putting Min Jong in.
민종씨를 넣을게요
What? Min Jong?
무엇? 민종?
Warm him up.
그를 따뜻하게 해주세요.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
Min Jong.
민종.
Yes?
예?
Let's get you warmed up.
몸을 따뜻하게 해주세요.
What?
무엇?
Relax, alright?
진정해, 알았지?
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
[Vikings 0 - 3 Dreams]
[바이킹 0 - 3 꿈]
- Your attention, please. - Huh?
- 많은 관심 부탁드립니다. - 응?
- From the top of the 6th inning, - Now pitching for the Dreams,
- 6회초부터 - 이제 꿈을 향해 투구하고 있습니다.
it seems pitcher Lim will take over.
임투수가 대신할 것으로 보인다.
Lim Min Jong.
임민종.
The highly anticipated, first pick rookie.
많은 기대를 모으고 있는 첫 번째 픽 신인.
How will he perform?
그는 어떻게 활약할 것인가?
Will he live up to everyone's expectations?
그는 모든 사람의 기대에 부응할 수 있을까요?
Min Jong.
민종.
Relax.
안심하다.
Manager. Min Jong is still...
관리자. 민종은 아직도...
I know.
알아요.
Yuki.
유키.
Be ready.
준비하세요.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
Go, Min Jong!
가, 민종아!
Calm down, calm down.
진정하세요, 진정하세요.
Relax, relax.
긴장을 풀어라, 긴장을 풀어라.
Steady, steady.
꾸준하고 꾸준해요.
Switching to a rookie on a three-run lead?
3점차 리드로 신인으로 전환?
Your team's looking down on us.
당신 팀이 우리를 무시하고 있어요.
Will he be okay?
그 사람은 괜찮을까요?
Let's trust the manager's decision.
매니저의 결정을 믿자.
Watch it!
조심해!
- Control your pitch! - Yeah, yeah.
- 피치를 제어하세요! - 응, 응.
Min Jong!
민종!
Min Jong! Take it easy.
민종! 진정하세요.
Min Jong! It's okay.
민종! 괜찮아요.
Alright, let's go.
좋아, 가자.
Ball four!
4번 공!
Oh no...
아 안돼...
He's pitched three consecutive walks.
그는 3연속 볼넷을 던졌다.
And now...
그리고 지금은...
The next batter is Kudo.
다음 타자는 쿠도다.
- You got four. - Yeah.
- 4개 있어요. - 응.
It's only a tie.
넥타이일 뿐입니다.
- We'll protect you. - Okay?
- 우리가 당신을 보호할 거예요. - 좋아요?
Okay.
좋아요.
Ball!
공!
Don't worry. Let him hit it.
괜찮아요. 그에게 치게 놔두세요.
Min Jong, relax.
민종아, 진정해.
Ball!
공!
Last one!
마지막!
Right.
오른쪽.
Calm down, calm down.
진정하세요, 진정하세요.
Time!
시간!
Are they calling a pitching change?
그들은 투수 변경을 요청하고 있습니까?
Kijima has been warming up in the bullpen.
키지마는 불펜에서 몸을 풀고 있다.
Nice ball!
좋은 공!
Min Jong.
민종.
I'm giving you a mission.
나는 당신에게 임무를 부여하고 있습니다.
Strike out Kudo.
쿠도를 스트라이크 아웃하세요.
- But I... - If you can't...
- 하지만 난... - 할 수 없다면...
They've taken the lead!
그들이 선두를 차지했습니다!
Alright!
괜찮은!
Grand slam!
그랜드 슬램!
Strike out Kudo.
쿠도를 삼진으로 삼진
- But I... - If you can't...
- 하지만 난... - 할 수 없다면...
Let him hit the home run.
그에게 홈런을 치게 해주세요.
- Yeah. - That's right.
- 응. - 좋아요.
- It's okay to get hit. - Gwenchana, gwenchana.
- 맞아도 괜찮아요. - 그웬차나, 그웬차나.
Alright, let's go!
좋아, 가자!
- Min Jong! - We got this!
- 민종! - 우리는 이것을 얻었다!
Gwenchana-yo.
그웬찬나요.
Naleul mid-eo. [Trust me]
날을 미드어. [나를 믿으세요]
Kudo's home run puts the Vikings in the lead.
Kudo의 홈런으로 Vikings가 선두에 올랐습니다.
No!
아니요!
Why are you smiling?
왜 웃고 있어요?
Huh?
뭐?
Not, "huh"! We're behind! We're losing!
아니, "응"! 우리는 뒤쳐져 있어요! 우리는지고 있어요!
- Yup. - "Yup"?
- 응. - "응"?
Kudo hit a grand slam home run!
쿠도가 만루홈런을 쳤습니다!
The Dreams are losing!
꿈이 지고 있어요!
- Yup. - He's a lost cause!
- 응. - 그는 길을 잃었어요!
Keep him in.
그를 가둬두세요.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
Kudo's bat sure makes a great sound.
쿠도의 배트는 확실히 좋은 소리를 낸다.
Huh?
뭐?
Why are you all grinning?
왜 다들 웃고 있어요?
We haven't suffered a hit like that in ages.
우리는 오랫동안 그런 타격을 입지 않았습니다.
You'd better prepare yourself for more.
더 많은 것을 준비하는 것이 좋습니다.
Nothing wrong with that.
아무 문제가 없습니다.
Huh? I'm not following.
뭐? 나는 따르지 않습니다.
Min Jong.
민종.
It's okay if they score a hit.
안타를 쳐도 괜찮다.
Just throw it down the middle. Trust me.
그냥 가운데로 던져버리세요. 나를 믿으세요.
Min Jong, calm down.
민종아, 진정해.
I know what I said, but isn't this a bit much?
내가 무슨 말을 했는지 알아요. 근데 이건 좀 아닌데?
Honestly, I'm worried.
솔직히 걱정됩니다.
The manager is looking one step ahead.
감독님은 한 발 앞서 나가고 계십니다.
Beyond the wins and losses.
승패를 넘어.
Strike!
스트라이크!
Batter out!
타자 아웃!
The game is now over.
이제 게임이 끝났습니다.
Today's game ended 7-7.
오늘 경기는 7-7로 끝났습니다.
- It's a tie. - A tie, huh?
- 동점입니다. - 넥타이죠?
I admit. The Dreams have gotten noticeably stronger.
나는 인정한다. 꿈 눈에 띄게 강해졌습니다.
I owe that in part to you.
나는 부분적으로 당신에게 빚을 지고 있습니다.
Thank you for the practice game.
연습게임 감사합니다.
Let's contend for the series this year.
올해 시리즈를 위해 경쟁합시다.
See you around.
나중에 뵙겠습니다.
- Thank you again. - Thank you.
- 다시 한번 감사드립니다. - 감사합니다.
- Make way for Mr. Ishikura! - I don't need the fanfare.
- 이시쿠라 씨에게 길을 비켜주세요! - 팡파르는 필요없어요.
Please, allow me this much.
이 정도만 허락해주세요.
The Vikings are now making their exit.
바이킹은 이제 퇴장하고 있습니다.
Please watch your step.
발걸음을 조심해 주세요.
I will guide you folks out.
제가 여러분을 안내해 드리겠습니다.
It seems Lim has overcome his yips.
임씨는 입덧을 극복한 것 같다.
The manager's tough love worked its magic.
매니저의 강인한 사랑이 마법을 부렸다.
He's starting to throw strikes.
그는 스트라이크를 던지기 시작했습니다.
Strikes lead to strikeouts.
파업은 삼진으로 이어진다.
Right.
오른쪽.
If you're pitching four balls, toss it straight-on instead.
공 4개를 던진다면 대신 똑바로 던져보세요.
Your team's defense has you covered.
팀의 방어가 당신을 덮었습니다.
Lim has taken a step forward.
임씨는 한 발 더 나아갔다.
So have the Dreams.
꿈도 꾸세요.
Oh! You finally smiled.
오! 마침내 당신은 웃었습니다.
- Shall we go? - Yes.
- 갈까요? - 예.
Where's Kikuchi?
키쿠치는 어디 있지?
I bet he left already.
나는 그가 이미 떠났다고 확신한다.
Min Jong!
민종!
Sugohaseyo. (Great work)
스고하세요. (훌륭해요)
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Sugohaseyo...
스고하세요...
We've got cold beer!
우리는 시원한 맥주를 마셨다!
I, the humble Kikuchi, have chosen a premium beer for you all.
나, 겸손한 키쿠치, 여러분을 위해 프리미엄 맥주를 선택했습니다.
Quit promoting yourself. The players are the stars today.
자신을 홍보하지 마세요. 오늘은 선수들이 스타입니다.
My apologies!
사과드립니다!
Alright, everyone, grab a beer!
자, 다들 맥주 한잔하세요!
GM, if you would.
GM, 원하신다면요.
Good game today.
오늘 좋은 게임.
Thank you, sir.
감사합니다.
Athletes.
운동 선수.
If the Dreams win the series this season,
Dreams가 이번 시즌 시리즈에서 우승한다면
it would be because of your hard work.
그것은 당신의 노력 때문일 것입니다.
Because you all have overcome adversity.
여러분 모두가 역경을 이겨냈기 때문입니다.
If the Dreams do not win,
Dreams가 이기지 못하면
then my inability to secure a better training field will be to blame.
그럼 내가 보안을 유지할 수 없어 더 나은 훈련 분야가 비난받을 것입니다.
If we lose, we all share the blame.
패배하면 우리 모두가 책임을 지게 됩니다.
Exactly.
정확히.
Guess we just have to win the series, right?
우리가 시리즈에서 우승하면 될 것 같은데요, 그렇죠?
Your response, GM?
당신의 반응은 GM입니까?
Understood.
이해했다.
Team.
팀.
Cheers!
건배!
Dreams! Dreams!
꿈! 꿈!
Steroids also have the effect of increasing bone strength.
스테로이드도 효과있어요 뼈의 힘이 증가하는 것입니다.
It would explain
설명이 되겠죠
how Sawada pitched over 200 innings for two consecutive years without injury.
사와다의 200이닝 이상 투구 2년 연속 부상 없이.
That was very insightful.
매우 통찰력이 있었습니다.
You may now leave.
이제 떠나셔도 됩니다.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
[Unknown Number]
[알 수 없는 번호]
Kudo.
쿠도.
You'll disappoint your fans.
팬들을 실망시킬 것입니다.
Just get to it.
그냥 해보세요.
Want me to keep quiet?
조용히 하시겠습니까?
Then pay up.
그럼 결제하세요.
Fine, but no more after this.
좋아요. 하지만 이 이후로는 더 이상은 안 돼요.
That's not for you to decide.
그건 당신이 결정할 문제가 아닙니다.
Damn it!
젠장!
You heard about the arrested dealer, right?
체포된 딜러 얘기는 들었죠?
Now I'm not doubting you.
이제 나는 당신을 의심하지 않습니다.
I only worry because you're good.
난 단지 당신이 착하기 때문에 걱정이에요.
I'm innocent.
나는 결백하다.
I see.
알겠어요.
I'll believe you.
나는 당신을 믿을 것입니다.
But not everyone on the team is so trusting.
하지만 팀의 모든 사람이 그렇게 신뢰하는 것은 아닙니다.
Prove to us that the rumors are baseless.
소문이 근거가 없다는 것을 우리에게 증명해 보세요.
Don't sweat it.
너무 걱정하지 마세요.
I'll protect you.
내가 당신을 보호할 것이다.
Excuse me, sir.
죄송합니다.
Kudo.
쿠도.
[Japanese Baseball League] [Owners' Meeting]
[일본야구연맹] [오너 모임]
I am Negishi, of the Yaoshima Dreams.
저는 야오시마 드림즈의 네기시입니다.
Folks, every team owner spends a fortune to run a team.
여러분, 모든 팀 오너 팀을 운영하는 데 많은 돈을 씁니다.
Yet because of these drug allegations,
하지만 이러한 마약 혐의로 인해
anxious days have continued.
불안한 나날이 계속됐다.
We are the victims of this drug issue.
우리는 이 마약 문제의 피해자입니다.
The perpetrators are the athletes, who succumbed to such substances.
가해자는 운동선수들이다. 그러한 물질에 굴복한 사람.
I believe discussions ought to be held
나는 토론이 이루어져야 한다고 생각해요
before these guilty athletes are revealed.
이 유죄 선수들이 밝혀지기 전에.
Hence I have called this meeting to order.
그래서 나는 이 모임을 소집하여 명령을 내렸습니다.
What sort of discussion was held today?
오늘은 어떤 토론이 이루어졌나요?
We debated on our penalizing criteria.
우리는 처벌 기준에 대해 토론했습니다.
Previously, violations would result in, either.
이전에는 위반하면 다음 중 하나가 발생합니다.
One, a reprimanding.
하나, 질책.
Two, a suspension of 1 to 10 games.
둘째, 1~10경기 출전 정지.
Three, a suspension of under one year.
셋째, 1년 미만의 자격정지.
Or four, an indefinite suspension.
또는 4번, 무기한 정지.
But we, the board, have made a revision.
그러나 우리 이사회는 수정을 했습니다.
From this point forth,
이 시점부터
all violations will result in a two-year suspension.
모든 위반이 발생합니다 2년 정지 상태에요.
This is quite the sudden change.
이는 그야말로 갑작스러운 변화다.
Will players accept that?
플레이어들이 이를 받아들일까요?
However, if players come forth of their own accord,
하지만 선수들이 나오면 스스로
they will only be suspended a year.
1년만 정지됩니다.
Therefore, Sawada...
그러니까 사와다...
Oh, pardon me.
아, 죄송합니다.
Did you just say Sawada?
방금 사와다라고 했나?
As in the pitcher for the Dreams?
드림즈의 투수처럼요?
No, of course not.
아니요, 물론 그렇지 않습니다.
I simply misspoke.
나는 단지 잘못 말한 것뿐이다.
We will formerly instate these changes another day.
우리는 이전에 이러한 변경 사항은 다른 날에 발생합니다.
That is all.
그게 전부입니다.
The Dreams owner called for this meeting.
드림스 소유주가 이 회의를 소집했습니다.
What do we make of this?
우리는 이것으로 무엇을 만들까요?
I believe it's a sign the Dreams are certain their players are clean.
나는 그것이 꿈이 확실하다는 신호라고 믿습니다. 그 선수들은 깨끗해요.
I see.
알겠어요.
Investigations regarding this client list are just about wrapping up as well.
이 고객 목록에 관한 조사 이제 막 마무리하려는 중이야.
If the Dreams truly are clean,
꿈이 정말 깨끗하다면
this revision of disciplinary action was an incredibly smart play.
이번 징계 개정 엄청나게 똑똑한 플레이였습니다.
Yet if there are steroid users on the Dreams,
그러나 Dreams Universe에 스테로이드 사용자가 있다면
President Negishi's decision would certainly backfire.
네기시 사장의 결단 확실히 역효과를 낳을 것입니다.
It seems the president suspects Sawada.
사장이 사와다를 의심하는 것 같습니다.
Sawada?
사와다?
Wait, he's guilty?
잠깐만요, 그 사람이 유죄인가요?
- Idiot! - Ow!
- 바보! - 아야!
Trust your own team!
당신의 팀을 믿으세요!
I'm sorry...
미안해요...
How does he maintain his stamina?
그는 어떻게 체력을 유지합니까?
You know it's a trade secret of his.
그 사람 영업비밀인거 아시죠?
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
응, 응, 응...
Dude, you called him over.
야, 네가 그 사람한테 전화했잖아.
Got anything else to air out?
방송할 게 더 있나요?
I just want to know where all that muscle comes from.
난 그냥 알고 싶어 그 근육은 다 어디서 나오는지.
I'm not satisfied unless I hit .300 with over 20 homers.
.300을 안타면 만족 못해요 홈런이 20개 이상이다.
If you can't even hit 20 home runs,
홈런 20개도 못 치면
you're better off retiring.
당신은 은퇴하는 것이 좋습니다.
- What? - Chill, chill...
- 무엇? - 진정해, 진정해...
First-rate players sure are on another level.
일류 선수들은 확실히 다른 수준에 있습니다.
Your investigation reports are coming in.
귀하의 조사 보고서가 접수되고 있습니다.
I can't wait to see the results.
나는 결과를보고 싶어요.
[11 years ago]
[11년 전]
Kudo.
쿠도.
Good evening.
좋은 저녁이에요.
It must be tough, working out so late.
늦게까지 운동해서 힘들겠어요.
I'm a fan of yours.
나는 당신의 팬입니다.
What? Really?
무엇? 정말?
Even if you're a no-namer now,
지금은 이름이 없더라도
you'll become a man who hits the triple milestone.
너는 남자가 될 거야 트리플 이정표를 달성한 사람.
Well, I'm honored.
영광이네요.
Still...
아직도...
Practice has its limits, right?
연습에는 한계가 있잖아요?
Kudo, how about we...
쿠도, 우리는 어때...
[Press Conference Regarding Steroid Usage]
[스테로이드 사용 관련 기자회견]
We will now begin this press conference.
이제 기자회견을 시작하겠습니다.
Though the JPB gave players an opportunity,
JPB가 선수들에게 기회를 주었지만
no athletes came forth about steroid usage.
스테로이드 사용에 관해 어떤 운동선수도 나오지 않았습니다.
If investigations prove otherwise,
조사 결과 그렇지 않은 것으로 판명되면
a two-year suspension will be imposed.
2년 자격 정지가 부과됩니다.
We shall now announce for each team
이제 각 팀별로 발표하겠습니다
the results of our careful investigation.
신중한 조사 결과
Champions.
챔피언.
Two players, found guilty.
두 명의 선수가 유죄 판결을 받았습니다.
Pelicans.
펠리컨.
One player.
한 선수.
Dears.
친애하는.
Two players.
두 명의 선수.
Sabres.
세이브르.
Vikings.
바이킹.
Five players.
5명의 플레이어.
Five players?
5명의 선수?
That's a huge blow to the Vikings.
이는 바이킹에게 큰 타격입니다.
As for us...
우리는...
Dreams.
꿈.
None.
없음
Yes!
예!
Just as I suspected.
내가 의심했던 것처럼.
Liar. I know you had your doubts.
거짓말쟁이. 나는 당신이 의심을 가지고 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
- Quit trying to make yourself look good. - Ouch, ouch!
- 자신을 멋지게 보이려고 노력하지 마세요. - 아야, 아야!
Ow, ow, ouch!
아, 아, 아야!
Wasn't expecting the headlock.
헤드락은 기대도 안했는데
- It hurts! Let me go! - Those who violated the rules
- 아파요! 날 보내줘! - 규칙을 위반한 자
- will be suspended for two years. - Ouch!
- 2년간 정지됩니다. - 아야!
Until now...
지금까지...
All's well that ends well, right?
다 괜찮아, 잘 끝나니까 그렇지?
Due to the severity of the situation, we shall strictly impose...
상황의 심각성으로 인해 우리는 엄격하게 부과할 것입니다...
Then how can Sawada pitch so well?
그렇다면 사와다는 어떻게 그렇게 공을 잘 던지는 걸까요?
Sawada is...
사와다는...
Come in.
들어오세요.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
All players from the Dreams were clean.
드림즈의 선수들은 모두 깨끗했습니다.
Including Sawada?
사와다도 포함?
I analyzed Sawada in particular detail
사와다를 구체적으로 분석해봤습니다
because his past two years were exceptionally successful.
왜냐하면 그의 지난 2년 동안 예외적으로 성공했습니다.
He was originally a pitcher who relied on fastballs and sliders.
원래는 투수였는데 패스트볼과 슬라이더에 의존했던 선수.
After being traded to the Vikings,
바이킹과 거래된 후,
he learned the changeup, adding more to his pitching repertoire.
체인지업을 배웠고, 그의 투구 레퍼토리에 더 많은 것을 추가합니다.
With the sheer variety he had under his belt,
그는 엄청난 다양성을 갖고 있었고,
his number of strikeouts soared.
그의 삼진 수가 급증했다.
Ultimately, he evolved into a monster who could pitch 20 winning games.
결국 그는 괴물로 진화했다. 20개의 승리 게임을 던질 수 있는 사람.
Dreams may be in last, but they're a clean team.
꿈은 마지막에 있을 수도 있고, 하지만 그들은 깨끗한 팀이에요.
I'm overjoyed to hear that.
나는 그 말을 듣고 매우 기뻤습니다.
What an absolute relief.
참으로 안도감이 듭니다.
Seeing your anger regarding drug use,
약물 사용에 대한 당신의 분노를 보고,
the public must have thought,
대중은 이렇게 생각했을 것임에 틀림없어
"Though they're weak, they're an honorable team."
"그들은 비록 약하지만 그들은 명예로운 팀이다."
I'm simply imitating you, GM.
나는 단지 당신을 흉내내는 것뿐입니다, GM.
I'm honored.
영광입니다.
In fact, I believe we'll make a fine team.
사실 저는 우리가 좋은 팀을 만들 것이라고 믿습니다.
I look forward to working with you.
나는 당신과 함께 일하기를 기대합니다.
So you were clean.
그래서 당신은 깨끗했습니다.
I guess that explains all the practicing you do.
그게 설명이 될 것 같아요 당신이 하는 모든 연습.
My bad.
내 잘못이야.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
Kudo, how about we...
쿠도, 우리는 어때...
I believed in Kudo.
나는 쿠도를 믿었다.
As did I.
나도 마찬가지였어.
He dedicated an extraordinary amount of time to practice.
그는 특별한 일을 헌신했다 연습할 시간.
He wouldn't have resorted to drugs.
그는 마약에 의지하지 않았을 것이다.
A long time ago, he was falsely flagged for a drug test.
오래 전, 그는 약물 검사를 위해 허위 신고를 받았습니다.
He still thinks I snitched on him.
그 사람은 아직도 내가 자기를 밀고했다고 생각하는 것 같아요.
So in retaliation, he cornered you with various lies,
그래서 보복으로, 그는 다양한 거짓말로 당신을 궁지에 몰아넣었어요
and got you kicked off the team.
그리고 당신은 팀에서 쫓겨났어요.
It's my fault for not clearing things up.
일을 정리하지 못한 것은 내 잘못이다.
Sawada.
사와다.
Yes?
예?
[Sawada]
[사와다]
[Ramen Tora]
[라면 토라]
Welcome.
환영.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Let's eat.
먹자.
This was always our meal before a big day.
이것은 중요한 날 전에 항상 우리의 식사였습니다.
You hit a home run in your debut game.
데뷔전에서 홈런을 쳤습니다.
I pitched a shutout in mine.
나는 내 입장에서 폐쇄를 선언했다.
Those were the days, huh?
그 시절이었죠, 그렇죠?
What're you trying to say?
무슨 말을 하려는 거야?
All the young players admired Tatsuya Kudo.
젊은 선수들은 모두 쿠도 타츠야를 존경했습니다.
Live with your head held high.
머리를 높이 들고 생활하십시오.
I want you to swing that bat with pride.
나는 당신이 그 배트를 자랑스럽게 휘두르기를 바랍니다.
At this rate, what will you tell your fans?
이대로라면 팬들에게 어떤 말을 전할 것인가?
Take responsibility.
책임을 져라.
I'm worried about you. As a friend.
나는 당신이 걱정됩니다. 친구로서.
Kudo.
쿠도.
How could an athlete who represents Japan
어떻게 일본을 대표하는 선수가
take part in illegal, online gambling?
불법 온라인 도박에 참여하시겠습니까?
Shut up! I'm not paying you a damn cent!
입 다물어! 난 너한테 한 푼도 안 줄 거야!
[GM Sakurazaki]
[GM 사쿠라자키]
[Japan Professional Baseball Organization]
[일본프로야구협회]
I haven't forgotten, alright?
난 잊지 않았어, 알았지?
Forgotten what?
무엇을 잊으셨나요?
Your threat!
당신의 위협!
So you've made up your mind.
그래서 당신은 결정했습니다.
Mr. Ishikura.
이시쿠라 씨.
A retired number will be difficult now, won't it?
은퇴한 번호 지금은 힘들겠지?
Allow me to ask you once more.
다시 한 번 묻도록 하겠습니다.
What is important to you?
당신에게 중요한 것은 무엇입니까?
Fans would sing your cheer song.
팬들은 당신의 응원가를 불러줄 것입니다.
Children would shout your name.
아이들은 당신의 이름을 외칠 것입니다.
The Dreams made you who you are today.
꿈이 지금의 당신을 만들었습니다.
Do you wish to retire with them?
그들과 함께 은퇴하고 싶나요?
If so...
그렇다면...
you must change.
당신은 변화해야합니다.
Cherish your teammates.
팀원을 소중히 여기세요.
Your top priority should be the team.
최우선 순위는 팀이어야 합니다.
Never put yourself first.
결코 자신을 먼저 생각하지 마십시오.
Always think of the team.
항상 팀을 생각하세요.
And lastly.
그리고 마지막으로.
Re-examine the other aspects in your life.
당신의 삶의 다른 측면을 재검토하십시오.
I'll ask again.
다시 질문하겠습니다.
Do you wish to retire with the Dreams?
드림즈와 함께 은퇴하고 싶나요?
I want to return to the Dreams.
나는 꿈으로 돌아가고 싶다.
I'll try negotiating with Mr. Ishikura.
이시쿠라 씨와 교섭을 시도해 보겠습니다.